could be a solution for risk management
address mitigation
that's a more value creating role for
insurance and that's something that
corporates would value much more than
just saying that you know earlier is
that's a partner
so that's a journey that we started back
in 2014 and part of the journey we
started the Indian risk management award
to recognize and
you know and reward individual
corporates who take the lead in this
management
our feeling was that in India you see
awards for you know business you see a
lot for leadership you see awards for
financial performance but you never had
an award for uh you know good risk
management strategy so that was the
thought process behind the Indian risk
management Awards which we will have
today in the evening
but after a few years management award
one of the response that we were getting
from warburtons was
have really taught us that lesson uh you
know across the world
but the feedback that we were getting
was that you know Wireless management is
important how do we qualify you know
what we're doing is there some way to
figure out
uh or build an index that tells us when
we stand uh within the industry or
across Industries
but this is not easy because risk is not
just the type of risk that we covered if
you look at a business there's a
multiple risks that you have to look at
and maybe there are models and indices
that looks at credit risks there are
models and indices that looks at uh you
know operational risk but at least we
didn't see across the world too many
comprehensive Risk Index that we felt
could be useful to look at you know
overall business decisions
you know and when he spoke to them they
had a concept that we jointly evolved
and then we worked together to you know
launch this Index this is the third year
you know the Suzuki will talk about the
key findings I'll not get into that
that's his domain but we are really
happy to partner with them and provide
this tool for Indian corporates
the launch of the index or the or the
the results of these studies this year
is not the ending itself I think the
whole Focus for us is that how do we
help Indian corporate with these inputs
you know become even better in their
risk management approach that's the
thought process but you know as always
there's all you know the way to start it
is to launch the index that's what we're
here for and from ICC longboards side
that we again welcome all of you uh you
thank you for joining us and look
forward to you know having a nice
session with you all of you thank you